https://www.thetreemaker.com/privacypolicy.html

The Tree Maker
Due to Covid-19 our hours of availability and order processing have been shortened to Mondays and Fridays only as we are a small family business. If you have any questions please email us at sales@thetreemaker.com for the fastest response possible. If you have concerns about processing times you may email those concerns prior to placing your order. We are working as fervently as possible on existing orders and appreciate your patience during this time. Thank you for your business. From our family to you and yours stay safe and blessings to you all.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your shopping experience as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use our Internet site as it is intended. For your entertainment!!
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how The Tree Maker and its affiliates collect information from all of our customers, and what we do with the information we collect. The Tree Maker requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.
Personal/Company Information and How It Is Used
The Tree Maker collects information in different ways from visitors who access our Website. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our services and, do not share this information with third parties unless it is with an affiliate that is helping us with your order.
On-Line Shopping
Our Web site allows you to purchase products. You will be asked to provide contact information, such as your company name, your personal name, address, "ship to" information, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information.
The Tree Maker and its affiliates will use the information you provide for two purposes, to process your order, or to contact you about previous inquirers. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order.
Responses to Email Inquiries
When Visitors send email inquiries to The Tree Maker and its affiliates, the return address is only used to answer the email inquiry we receive. We do not use the return email address for any other purpose and will not share the return email address with any third party.
The Tree Maker's Commitment to Data Security
The Tree Maker and its affiliates, have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our website and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.
Where to Direct any Questions you may have about The Tree Maker and its affiliates' Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact:
The Tree Maker
P.O. Box 128, Cedar Hill, TN 37032
Email: sales@thetreemaker.com
Toll Free 866-480-0202
Revisions to This Policy
The Tree Maker and its affiliates reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted in accordance with standard Internet Service policies.
Family Crest - Alphabetic Surname Listings
A|
B|
C|
D|
E|
F|
G|
Asked Questions" section before ordering.
It covers a number of subjects in detail. Most of the questions
are in regards to customization to family tree charts, family coat
of arms, family crest symbol, Design
Your Own Coat of Arms Symbol, surname history, family rings,
and last name meaning, but the first few apply to everyone. This
will help avoid any problems that could arise about your order.
Free pedigree chart if needed. These
family tree products make great birthday
gifts, Christmas presents,
or a Wedding and Anniversary
gift.
Copyright
©2001-2020 All Rights Reserved, The Tree Maker, PO Box 128, Cedar Hill, TN. 37032
privacy
policy l merchant policy
